ghirardelli.com 2017-06-06

# Website Privacy Policy for Ghirardelli

At Ghirardelli, we value your privacy. To make our advertising efforts more relevant and useful for you, we sometimes utilize 3rd party companies to target ads that reflect your interests, based on past browsing behavior.

  1. ####### Our Privacy Promise

Ghirardelli will not collect any personally identifiable information about you—such as your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address («personal information»)—through our Web site unless you provide it to us voluntarily. You are not required to register or otherwise «sign in» to browse and enjoy our site.

  2. ####### Personal Information

This is the official Web site of Ghirardelli Chocolate Company (”Ghirardelli”), makers of premium chocolates. We at Ghirardelli respect your concerns about privacy. Accordingly, we have enacted the following policies which are intended to protect your privacy and ensure that all voluntarily submitted personal information is handled in a safe and responsible manner. As we continue to develop our Web site and take advantage of technologies to improve the services we provide, our policies will continue to evolve in order to maintain the same standards of privacy protection.

  3. We only collect personal information when you request our services, and only use the information collected to provide that service for you. If you choose to make a purchase, you will be asked to provide contact information (such as your name and shipping address) and financial information (such as your credit card number and expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to process your order. We may also contact you via email or regular mail from time-to-time to keep you up-to-date on Ghirardelli or to send you our latest catalog. If you send a gift and provide the recipient's shipping address, or send a gift certificate and provide the recipient's e-mail address, this information is used for delivery purposes. We will not contact a recipient directly via email or catalog. When requesting a service, you may also choose to receive updates and special offers (”Ghirardelli Email List”) from the Ghirardelli Chocolate Company and its promotional partners. Like all services provided through our Website, the choice to receive Ghirardelli newsletters is optional, and you may change your preference at any time.
  4. Any personal information provided will not be sold, rented, traded, or otherwise shared with anyone outside of Ghirardelli, or used for reasons beyond those contemplated by this statement. None of Ghirardelli's assistants (such as our shipping or credit card company) retain, share, store, or use personal information for any reason other than providing the requested service.
  5. ####### Access to Personal Information

Our goal is to provide our customers with the best service possible. To do this, we need to make sure that our information is accurate, current, and reliable for its intended use. If your personal information changes or if you no longer wish to receive our newsletters, you may correct, amend, or delete your account information at any time. As we continue to globalize our Web services, we hope to provide online access capabilities to all of our users. At present, corrections, amendments, and deletions should be handled by updating your information in My Account, unsubscribing from our email list through the “unsubscribe” link provided in the email, or contacting Ghirardelli directly. Contact information is located in the Contact Us page.

  6. We allow some of our business partners to place their logo and a link on our Web site if we think their business may be of interest to you. Please be aware that even though we try to choose partners who adhere to similar privacy standards and practices, we cannot control their use of cookies in relation to these links. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy policies of all the sites you visit.
  7. ####### Security

Ghirardelli takes every precaution to protect our customers' information. When you submit personal information, it is protected both online and offline. Whether you purchase a product, send a gift, or sign up for Ghirardelli emails, you do so under up-to-date encryption/security policies and technological safeguards. All personal information is collected pursuant to these standards and is secured in databases for the sole and exclusive use of Ghirardelli. Only those who need the information to perform a specific job (such as our billing clerks or customer service representatives) are granted access to personal information. Questions regarding our privacy policy, enforcement procedures, or security measures can be answered at any time by contacting Customer Service. Contact details are available on the Contact Us page.
